[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This artistic and architectural movement, formed by Vladimir Tatlin, dismissed pure art in favor of art used as an instrument for social purposes.", "correct_answer": "Constructivism", "incorrect_answers": ["Production Art", "Structural Art", "Dadaism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what type of tube is blood drawn for a substance abuse test?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Light blue", "Dark Green", "Small Lavender"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term refers to a kind of unfiltered beer, conditioned and served from the cask without additional pressure.", "correct_answer": "cask ale beer", "incorrect_answers": ["cask draught beer", "cask lager beer", "cask rye beer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Wyler is unique among the AFI directors because there was a  20-year gap between his  earliest and latest classic movies on the Top 100 List.. What are the two movies?", "correct_answer": "Wuthering Heights and Ben-Hur", "incorrect_answers": ["Wings and Waynes World", "Wuthering Heights and The Best Years of Our Lives", "The Birth of a Nation and Ben-Hur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fyodor Tyutchev, Nikolai Alekseevich Nekrasov and Evgeny Baratynsky were Russian poets and are usually related to this period of Russian literature.", "correct_answer": "19th century", "incorrect_answers": ["Silver Age", "Post-Soviet era", "Soviet era"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This food is a very good source of energy. It also contains phenylethylamine, which triggers the same reaction in the body as falling in love does.", "correct_answer": "Chocolate", "incorrect_answers": ["Honey", "Beeswax", "Sugar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The red rose is a symbol of this political ideology.", "correct_answer": "Socialism", "incorrect_answers": ["Monarchism", "Liberalism", "Democracy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In astrophysics, which theorem defines what parameters black holes are characterized by?", "correct_answer": "Black holes have no hair", "incorrect_answers": ["No-ghost theorem", "Brouwers Fixed point theorem", "Hairy ball theorem"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This material on the surface of a lithosphere is the subject of study of pedology.", "correct_answer": "soil", "incorrect_answers": ["turf", "rock", "rain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a patient has chest pain and ST elevation in nearly all leads of the EKG, what is the likely diagnosis?", "correct_answer": "Pericarditis", "incorrect_answers": ["Acute Myocardial Infarction", "Pulmonary Embolism", "Pneumothorax"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What two gases comprise the greater part of the Sun?", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen and helium", "incorrect_answers": ["Oxygen and hydrogen", "Nitrogen and hydrogen", "Nitrogen and oxygen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these nominated actresses won the Razzie Award for Worst Actress for her role in the 1983 movie The Lonely Lady?", "correct_answer": "Pia Zadora", "incorrect_answers": ["Linda Blair", "Olivia Newton-John", "Faye Dunaway"]}]